ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4014
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files
1966-1985
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Office of the Dean
Moore, David G.
Risley, Robert F.
McKersie, Robert B.
/4014
26.11 cubic feet
26.1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
School administration files, building files, extension files, fiscal files, correspondence, legislation files, publication lists and research development files are included in this collection.
3079847
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 21, 2016
Scope and Contents
Records are filed according to the Records Retention Schedule codes:
A-1 through A-26: School administrative files.
B: Building files.
CU-1 through CU-63: University files.
E: Extension files.
FS: Fiscal files.
G-1 through G-50: Correspondence.
IN: Institutes.
I: Industrial Education.
L: Library.
Leg.: Legislation files.
M-1 through M-32: Institutes and Conferences.
PR: Projects.
PU: Publications and Distributions.
R: Research Development files.
ST-1 through ST-10: Undergraduate student education files.
ST-19 through ST26: Graduate student education files.
ST-30 through ST-35: Alumni.
ST-39 through ST-51: Schedules and Program Planning.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3006: ILR School Dean's Office Publications /3085: ILR School Dean's Office Files /4010: ILR School Fiscal Office Files /4028: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Records /4054: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Files /4070: ILR School Dean's Office Additional Personnel Files /4082: ILR School Dean's Office Records /4100: ILR School Dean's Office "Report of the ILR Review Panel" Background Documentation /4144: ILR School Dean's Office Files Additional
Moore, David G.; Risley, Robert F. (Robert Francis), 1922-; McKersie, Robert B.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Dean's Office; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Administration.
3079847
- A-2: ILR Policies & Procedures (Space & Facilities for Retired Professors, Loyalty Oath, Procedures for Requesting Leaves, Payroll certification, sick leave, personal leave, vacation reporting, holidays, summer work schedule, hours of work, Confer (Box 1)
  - Geneva Trip August 23-September 9, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - November 7, 1970 - 25th Anniversary Dinner Statler Inn Ballroom (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - December 11, 1970 - 25th Anniversary Dinner for Labor (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - A-2-2 25th Anniversary Year 1970 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - A-2-3 1969-70 Organization, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - A-3 Council Meeting October 23, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - A-3 Council Meeting April 17-18, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - A-3 Council Meeting November 19, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - A-3 Council Meeting April 18-19, 1974 Ithaca (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - A-3 Council Meeting November 8, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - A-3 Council Meeting April 12-13, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - A-3 Council Meeting November 30, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - A-3 Council Meeting May 17, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - A-3 Council Meeting Feb. 4-5, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - A-3 Council Meeting November 10, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - A-3 Council Meeting October 7, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - A-3 Council Meeting April 20, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - A-3 Council Meeting January 12, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - A-3 Council Meeting November 6-7, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - A-3 Council Meeting April 23, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - A-3 Council Meeting November 7, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Spec. Council Comm. Mtg. w/ Gould, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - A-3 Council Meeting May 16, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - A-3-1 Rpts. To Bd. Trustees on Council, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - A-3-4 Membership and Agenda (Council Meetings), 1971 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - A-3-5 Littlewood Memorial, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - A-3-7 Statutory Colleges Joint Council Meetings, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- A-4-A: Administrative Conferences. 1971-1975. (Box 2)
  - A-4-a State Univ. Policies (General) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - A-4-a State Univ. Policies (General), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - A-4b SUNY Faculty Senate - 1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - A-4c -- Misc. (SUNY) 1966 to date (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - A-4d State University Master Plan, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - A-4-d 1972 State Univ. Master Plan (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - A-4d State University Master Plan, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - A-4f Tuition (State University), 1963 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - A-4-1 Board Trustees State U. of N.Y., 1975 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - A-4-1 Minutes of Board Trustees '71-'72, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - A-4-1 Minutes of Board of Trustees (1970-71), 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- A-4-1: Board of Trustees, Minutes of the Board of Trustees. 1966-1975. (Box 3)
  - A-4-1 Minutes of Board of Trustees, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - A-4-2 State College Deans and Policy, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - A-4-5 --State University Construction Fund 1964 Report (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - A-4-7 Institute for Public Policy Altern., 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - A-4-8 Special Committees (SUNY), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - A-5 Faculty Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Meetings 1974-75, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - A-5 Faculty Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - A-5 1972-73 Faculty Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - A-5 1971-72 Faculty Meetings, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - A-5 1970-71 Faculty Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - A-5 1969-70 Faculty Meetings, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - A-5 -- 1968-69 Faculty Meetings, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - A-5 -- 1967-68 Faculty Meetings, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - A-5 -- 1966-67 Faculty Meetings, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - A-5.1 Faculty/Staff Activities, 1964-1974 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - A-5-2 Faculty Legislation Past, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- A-5-3: Middle States Evaluation (Accreditation). 1969-1975. (Box 4)
  - A-5-4 Convocations, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - A-5-5 Long-Range Planning (Provost Plane - 1970) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - A-5-5 Long-Range Planning Report (1960) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - A-5-5 Long-Range Planning Report (1960) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - A-5-6 ILR Report to Centennial Planning Committee, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - A-5-7 Academic Plan, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - A-5-7 -- Academic Plan, Revision 1968 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - A-5-7 Academic Plan 1966 Revised (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - A-5-8 Master Calendar Information, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - A-5-9 State Relations Committee, etc., 1976 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - A-6 ILR Committees (General) (1964 to date) (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - A-6-1 Extension Committee, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - A-6-1 Extension Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - 1967-68 Review of Status of Extension Personnel, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - A-6-3 Faculty Personnel Policies Committee, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - A-6-3 Personnel Policies Committee, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Planning and Personnel Policies Committee (1968- A-6-3 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Planning and Personnel Policies Committee (1967) A-6-3 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Minutes of Long Range Planning and Personnel Policies Com. Mtgs. A-6-3 (1963- (Box 4, Folder 19)
- A-6-3a: Staff Personnel Policies. 1969-1975. (Box 5)
  - A-6-3a Staff Personnel Policies Committee, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - A-6-5 Graduate Committee (1970- (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - A-6-6 Editorial Board ILR Review, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - A-6-7 Library Committee, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - A-6-8 Nominations and Elections Committee, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - A-6-9 Planning Committee (Regular), 1975 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - A-6-9 ILR Planning Material 1974-75, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - A-6-10 Research and Publications Committee, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - A-6-13 Undergraduate Program Committee 1971- (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - A-6-14 Visitors, Lecturers, and Public Events, 1969-1974 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Academic Standards Committee, 1969-1974 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- A-6-19: ?. 1968-1975. (Box 6)
  - A-6-19 Academic Integrity Committee, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - A-6-20 Advisory Committee for Audiovisual Activities, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - A-6-20 - Advisory Council-Faculty Cmte. ILR Expans. In NYC, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Computer Funds in Research, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - A-6-20 - Labor College Advisory Committee, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - A-6-20 - Computer Use in the Classroom, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - A-6-20 Ad Hoc. Committee on "War on Waste", 1975 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - A-7-a -- Faculty Activities Survey, 1956-1957 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - A-7-1 Personnel Changes, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - A-7-21 - Sabbatic Leaves - Current, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - A-7-3 -- New Faculty Members (General), 1976 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - A-7-4 Travel to Professional Meetings, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - A-7-5 Private Consulting, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - A-7-7 Fellowships, 1953-1969 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - A-8 Dean's Report to President 1971-72, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - A-8 Dean's Report - ILR Highlights 1970-71, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - A-8 -- Dean's Report-- ILR Highlights 1969-70, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - A-8 ILR Highlights 1968-69, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - A-10 ILR Staff Organization, 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - A-10-1 -- Non-Professional Staff, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - A-10-2 ILR Office Procedures, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - A-10-3 Materials Lab, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - A-10-4 ILR Distribution Center, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - A-10-5 Janitorial Service, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - A-10-6 ILR Mail Room, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - A-10-7 Fiscal Office, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - A-10-8 ILR Personnel Officer, 1973-1976 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- A-11: Adm. Conf. (General) (Ind. Adm. Retreats). 1965-1975. (Box 7)
  - A-11 Administrative Conferences 1973-74, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - A-11 Administrative Conferences 1972-73, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - A-11 Administrative Conferences 1971-72, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - A-11 Administrative Conferences 1969-70, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - A-11-a Student -Adm. Conference, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - A-11-1 Adm. Conf. on Resident Instr. + Student Rel., 1969 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - A-11-2 Adm. Conf. Extension + Public Service, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - A-11-3 Adm. Conf. on School Rel. + Devel. Activities, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - A-11-4 Adm. Conf. on Fiscal control, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - A-12 ILR News, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - A-19 Division Directors, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - A-19a Report of Division Directors, 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - A-19a Report of Division Directors, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - A-19a Reports of Division Directors, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - A-19a Reports of Division Directors 1969-70, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - A-19a Reports of Division Directors, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - A-19a Report of Division Directors, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - A-19-a -- Report of Division Directors (1967) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - A-20 Office of Resident Instruction, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - A-20 Office of Resident Instruction Recruiting, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - A-20 Office of Resident Instruction 1967 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - A-21 Extension, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - A-22 Research Support, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - A-22 Research Development, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- A-23: Library Committee. 1965-1975. (Box 8)
  - A-23 Library, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - A-24 International, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - A-26 School Relations, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - A-26a Placement, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - A-26b Public Relations, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - A-26-1 Individual Program Information, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - A-27 School Services Unit, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - A-27-1 School Mailing Lists and Procedures, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Institutional Development and Fund Raising, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - A-29 Associate Dean Windmuller, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - A-30 Executive Staff, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - CU-1 Cornell Associates Council, Corp. Com., and Found, Gifts, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - CU-1-2 C.U. Admin. Board (1963 to date) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - CU-2 Board of Trustees, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - CU-2-1 Trustees Comm. On Cornell-SUNY Relation, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - CU-2-2 State Relations Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - CU-2-3 Trustees Committees General, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - CU-3 Statutory Coll. Deans Meetings, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - CU-3 Deans' Meetings 1969- (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - CU-3-1 Dean's Council 7/1974 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - CU-3-1 Deans' Council, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- CU-4: Cornell University: Fiscal--Tuition Charges (Graduate Assistant Tuition Waiver (see also ST-20), Tuition waivers for out-of-state endowment fund write-ups, Treas.- L. Durland, Tuition increase 1969, 1970). 1969-1975. (Box 9)
  - CU-4 Fiscal, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - CU-5 Policies and Procedures, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - CU-5-1 Order of Succession, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - CU-6 University Committees A-D, 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - CU-6 University Committees E-G, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - CU-6 University Committees H-L, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - CU-6 University Committees M-R, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - CU-6 University Committees S-T, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- CU-6(cont): University Committees cont.. 1969-1975. (Box 10)
  - CU-6 University Committees U-Z, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - CU-7 Univ. Development and Relations (1963 to date) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - CU-8 1974-75 University Faculty, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - CU-8 1973-74 University Faculty, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - CU-8 University Faculty 1971/72, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - CU-8 University Faculty 1970/71, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - CU-8 1969-1970 University Faculty (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - CU-8-1 - Correspondence (University Faculty), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - CU-8-1a Professors-at-Large, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - CU-8-1b Faculty Council, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - CU-8-2 University Counsel, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - CU-8-3 -- By-Laws (Cornell University), 1975 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - CU-9 President's Office 7/1974 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - CU-9 Pres. Dale R. Corson, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - CU-9a Asst. to the President for Cont. Education (Barlow), 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - CU-9b Financial Task Forces '75, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - CU-9-c Senior Vice President, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- CU-9-1a: Vice President for Administration (Brown, 1968; Lawrence, 1970).. 1969-1975. (Box 11)
  - CU-91a Vice President for Administration (1970-) Samuel A. Lawrence, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - CU-9-1b Vice President for Research, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - CU-9-1c Vice President for Public Affairs, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - CU-9-3 Provost's Office R.A. Plane, Acting Prvt. (1969- (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - CU-9-3-1 Vice Provost Robert F. Risley, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - CU-9-3-1 W. Keith Kennedy, Vice Provost, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - CU-9-4 Cornell Regional Offices, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - CU-12 -- Computer Center, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - CU-12-1 University Computing Board, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - CU-13 Division of Mgmt. Systems and Analysis, 1968-1974 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - CU-14 Office of Reg. Studies and Dev., 1967 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - CU-15 April 1969 Emergency (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - CU-15-1 Cornell Consultant Assembly, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - CU-15-2 Fall 1969 Moratoriums (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - CU-15-3 April 1970 Events (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - CU-16 Univ. Ombudsman, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - CU-20 Admissions Office (1969- (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - CU-21 Aeronautical Laboratory, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Association (1964 to date) (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - CU-23 Buildings and Properties, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - CU-23a Center for International Studies, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - CU-23a Center for International Studies (1969- (Box 11, Folder 22)
- CU-10: General (could include: School and/or College Announcements; Commencement Arrangements; United Fund Drive; Three-Year Calendar; Charter Day; Cornell Day; Convocations).. 1968-1975. (Box 12)
  - CU-10 General, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - CU-11 Distinguished Visitors Program, 1962-1973 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - CU-24 Clinic, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - CU-25 CURW (1963 to date) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - CU-26 Dean of Men and Dean of Women, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - CU-27 Financial Aids Office, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - CU-28 Foreign Students Office, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - CU-29 Library (1969- (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - CU-29-1 Cornell Program in Oral History, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - CU-30 Military Training and Physical Education, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - CU-31 Office of Public Information, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - CU-31-1 Office of Community Relations, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - CU-32 Personnel Office, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - CU-32-A Placement Service, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - CU-32-1 University Employee Relations, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - CU-32-2 Affirmative Action Program, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - CU-32-2a Affirmative Action Advisory Board, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - CU-32-3 University Personnel Council, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - CU-32-4 Manpower Planning and Personnel Policy Board, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - CU-33 Traffic and Parking (1969- (Box 12, Folder 20)
- CU-33: Traffic & Parking. 1957-1975. (Box 13)
  - CU-33a Travel Office, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - CU-34 Williard Straight, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - CU-35 Student Committees, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - CU-35a Student Publications, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - CU-36 University Testing Service Bureau, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - CU-37 Office of Educational Development, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - CU-40 Agriculture (1963 to Date) (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - CU-41 Arts and Sciences, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - CU-41a Women's Studies Program, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - CU-42 Architecture, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - CU-43 B and PA School (1964 to Date) (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - CU-43a Sloan Institute B and PA (1964 to Date) (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - CU-44 Center for Improvement of Undergraduate Education, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - CU-45 Engineering, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - CU-46 Graduate School (1963 to Date) (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - CU-47 Human Ecology, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - CU-48 Hotel Administration, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - CU-49 Law, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - CU-50 Medical, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - CU-51 Nursing, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - CU-51a - Nutrition (Grad. School of, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - CU-52 Veterinary, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - CU-53 Unclassified Student Division, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - CU-54 Africana Studies and Center, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - CU-55 Center for Urban Development, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - CU-56 COSEP Program, 1956-1971 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- CU-60: Biological Science Division. 1965-1975. (Box 14)
  - CU-60 Biological Science Division (1963 to date) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - CU-61 Water Resource Center, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - CU-62 Center for Environmental Quality Managements, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - CU-63 Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - E-1- Budget and Fiscal (Extension), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - E-1-1 Contracts and Agreements, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - E-1-2 Lack of Funds, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - E-2 - Policies and Procedures (ext.), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - E-3 - Staff Meetings (Extension), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - E-4 Advisory Committee on Labor Education 1969- (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - E-4-1 Adv. Comm. On Public Employment, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - E-4-2 Management Advisory Committee, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - E-4-3 Railway Labor Education Council, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - E-5 - Correspondence rel. courses and Program (ext.), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - E-5-1 ext. Summary of Programs, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - E-5-2 Individual Program Information, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - E-5-2a Annual Institute for Training Specialists, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - E-5-3 ILR Conference Calendar, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - E-5-4 Reports on Extension Programs, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - E-6 Part-time Ext. Teachers, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - E-6-1 - Fiscal Policies for Part-Time Ext. Teachers, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - E-8 - Exhibits for Fairs, Labor Union Conventions, etc., 1975 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - E-10 - Staffing (Extension), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - E-11 N.Y.C. Office, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- E-12: ?. 1965-1975. (Box 15)
  - E-12a Labor Studies Program General, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - E-12a Labor Studies Personnel, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - E-12b Labor Studies Budget, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - E-12-1 Labor Studies Program (NYC), 1974 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - E-12-2 Labor Studies Program (Buffalo), 1975 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - E-12-3 Labor Studies Program (Rochester), 1975 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - E-12-4 Labor Studies Program, (Long Island), 1975 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - E-18 Western District Office, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - E-12-5 Labor Studies Albany, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - E-12-6 Railway Labor Studies Program, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - E-13 Management Studies Program, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Alice Grant Rochester Center (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - E-15 -- Audio Visual and TV Program, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - E-15-1 Labor Relations Cassette of the Month, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - E-16 -- Four State Colleges (Cooperation in Extension and Admission, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - E-17 Central District Office, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - E-20 - General File (Extension), 1973 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - E-21 ILR Extension Programming for Companies (Hodges) (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - E-22 Economic Education Center, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - IN-1 -- Institute of International Indus. And Labor Relations, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - IN-1-1 -- Cornell Turin International Centre Program, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - IN-2 - Institute of Public Employment 1973-, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- IN-2(cont): Institute of Public Employment (cont.). 1967-1975. (Box 16)
  - IN-2 -- Institute of Public Employment, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - In-3 Institute of Collective Bargaining, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - L-1 -- Budget and Fiscal --, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - L-2 - Policies and Procedures (Library, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - L-3-1 - Labor-Mgt. Documentation Center (Reports) (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - L-3-2 Jt. Labor History Proj. (United Transportation Union), 1973 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - L-3 - Correspondence (Labor-Mgt. Documentation Center), 1973 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - L-3-3 Conrail - Railroad Research Prog. Finch, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - L-4 Long Range Library Plans, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - L-5 Staff Recruitment, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - L-5-1 Selection of Librarian (1969_ (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - L-6 Relationship with Social Sciences, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - L-7 Centralized Information Systems, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - L-7-2 -- Reference Memorandum, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - L-8 Catherwood Center, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - L-9 IRC Library Collection, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- B-1-2: Maintenance and Repair. 1965-1975. (Box 17)